mymusicstaff.com 2014-05-07

# Privacy Policy - My Music Staff » My Music Staff

This Privacy Policy outlines the types of personal information we gather when you use MyMusicStaff.com as well as some of the steps we take to safeguard it.

The following principles apply to the personally identifying information we ask for and that you provide. “Personally identifying information” is information that individually identifies you, such as your name, physical address or email address.

## Data collection

• MyMusicStaff.com collects limited information your browser makes available whenever you visit our website. This information includes your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your query and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. We use this information to operate, develop and improve our services.

• Some of our services require you to register for an account. MyMusicStaff.com asks you for some personal information in order to create an account and we will use that information to provide the service. For certain services we may request credit card or other payment information which we do not maintain once the transaction has been completed.

## Cookies

Upon your first visit to MyMusicStaff.com, a cookie is sent to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser.

A “cookie” is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service and to better understand how people interact with us. MyMusicStaff.com does this by storing user preferences in cookies and by tracking user trends and patterns of how people search.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some MyMusicStaff.com features or services may not function properly without cookies.

MyMusicStaff.com uses the following cookies:

**Google Analytics** : This cookie allows us to view data on user website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on the website. The information is de-personalized and displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This helps to protect your privacy.

**DoubleClick:** We use remarketing codes to log when users view specific pages, allowing us to provide targeted advertising in the future.

Using the ads settings you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads. You can opt out from Google Analytics for Display and customized Google Display Network ads [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/).

## Information sharing

• We do not rent or sell your personally identifying information to other companies or individuals. We may share such information in any of the following limited circumstances:

• We have your consent.

• We provide such information to trusted businesses or persons for the sole purpose of processing personally identifying information on our behalf (i.e. processing a credit-card transaction).

• We conclude that we are required by law or have a good faith belief that access, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of MyMusicStaff.com.

• If you have an account, we may share the information submitted under your account among all of our services in order to provide you with a seamless experience and to improve the quality of our services. We will not disclose your account information to other people or non-affiliated companies, except in the limited circumstances described in this Policy or with your consent.

• We may store and process personal information collected on our site in Canada or any other country in which MyMusicStaff.com maintains facilities. By using our services, you consent to the transfer of your information among these facilities, including those located outside your country.

## Information security

• We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.

• We restrict access to your personally identifying information to employees who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services.

## Updating your information

• We provide mechanisms for updating and correcting your personally identifying information for our services.

## Changes to this Policy

Please note this Privacy Policy will change from time to time. We expect most such changes to be minor, but there may be changes that are more significant. Regardless, we will post those changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will also provide a more prominent notice. Each version will be noted at the bottom of the page.

If you have any additional questions, please feel free to us any time. _Last Revised:  January 2, 2014_
